Indar Joko Prasetyo

indarjoko89@gmail.com +6282260806240 Depok, West Java, ID

Summary

an experienced in IT related fields for almost 7 years with deeply understanding in technical support, Linux and open source environment. Also have 1 year experienced as visual designer that creates graphic design and user interface design. Portfolio can be seen at https://indarjoko.netlify.app, https://indarjo

Experience

Design & Code Freelancer

Self-Employed 12/2021 - Present

Create design and code for client needs.

Freelance Mentor

Glints ExpertClass 11/2021 - Present

Create and sharing presentation material about specific content especially in UI/UX Design.

Visual Designer

Boer Technology 12/2020 - 12/2021

Create user interface design and graphic design such as mobile app and website UI design, social media design, and posters.

Office Coordinator

Boer Technology 03/2019 - 11/2020

Managed company assets inventory and support another team for filled their needs.

IT Technical Support

Yayasan Pendidikan Madania Indonesia / Madania School 04/2014 - 02/2019

Helping employees and teachers to solve hardware & software-related problems and manage and maintenance IT assets inventory.

Skills

- UI/UX
- Wireframing
- HTML
- Wordpress

- Problem Solving
- Prototyping
- CSS
- Linux

Education Computer Science

STMIK Nusa Mandiri 09/2012 - 04/2014

Bachelor Degree with 3.03 GPA (Scale 4)

Computer Engineering

AMIK Bina Sarana Informatika 09/2007 - 02/2010

Associate Degree with 3.21 GPA (Scale 4)

Language

Indonesian

English

Teaching Experience

Basic Differences Between Graphic Designer and UI Designer (Glints ExpertClass 2021)

How to Gain Skills as A UI Designer (Glints ExpertClass 2022)

Certification

Android Basic: User Interface and User Input by Indonesia Android Kejar 2018

UX Concepts by Brainbench 2019

Programming Essential in Python by Digital Talent Scholarship Kominfo 2019

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula by Dicoding Academy 2019

Fullstack Designer by BuildWith Angga 2020

Merancang Produk yang Dicintai Pengguna Berdasarkan Data by Skill Academy 2020

Dasar-dasar Merancang Aplikasi yang Mudah Digunakan oleh Pengguna by Skill Academy 2020

Memulai Pemrograman dengan Python by Dicoding Academy 2020

WordPress Pro Course by Niagahoster 2021

Intro to Product Management by RevoU 2021

Project

Work Project

- ADINUSA Mobile App UI Design https://s.id/ADINUSAAppStore,
 https://s.id/ADINUSAPlayStore
- Btech Website Redesign https://btech.id

Freelance Project

- Kode Creative Hub (Design & Code) https://kodecreative.netlify.app/
- NWO Landing Page https://nwolanding.netlify.app/

Personal Project

- Behance https://behance.net/indarjoko
- Uplabs Premium Seller https://uplabs.com/indarjoko/
- Dribbble https://dribbble.com/indarjoko
- Github https://github.com/indarjoko